{"items": [{"question": "justice, fairness", "answer": "equity", "options": ["inequity", "equity", "iniquity", "equinox"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "injustice, unfairness", "answer": "inequity", "options": ["inequity", "iniquity", "equinox", "equanimity"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Absence of moral or spiritual values", "answer": "iniquity", "options": ["equanimity", "equinox", "equability", "iniquity"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "when day and night are of equal length, happens twice a year", "answer": "equinox", "options": ["equanimity", "equinox", "equability", "equilibrium"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "mental or emotional stability", "answer": "equanimity", "options": ["equilateral", "equability", "equilibrium", "equanimity"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "free from many changes or variations, uniform", "answer": "equability", "options": ["equability", "equilateral", "equestrian", "equilibrium"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "a state of balance due to the equal action of opposing forces.", "answer": "equilibrium", "options": ["equilibrium", "equestrienne", "equestrian", "equilateral"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "having all the sides equal", "answer": "equilateral", "options": ["equine", "equilateral", "equestrienne", "equestrian"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "someone on a horse", "answer": "equestrian", "options": ["equestrian", "equestrienne", "equerry", "equine"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "a woman who rides horses.", "answer": "equestrienne", "options": ["equerry", "equine", "equestrienne", "vociferous"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "resembling a horse", "answer": "equine", "options": ["vocalize", "vociferous", "equerry", "equine"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A personal attendant of the British royal family", "answer": "equerry", "options": ["vocalist", "vocalize", "vociferous", "equerry"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "crying out noisily clamorous.", "answer": "vociferous", "options": ["vocalize", "vocalist", "vociferous", "equity"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "give voice to", "answer": "vocalize", "options": ["equity", "vocalist", "vocalize", "inequity"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "a singer.", "answer": "vocalist", "options": ["inequity", "vocalist", "iniquity", "equity"], "answer_index": 2}], "title": "Session 21.txt", "total": 15}